Hamada ali

Web Developer three Years experience Flutter Developer One Year experience

Address:

Cairo - Nasr city - Egypt

Phone:

+201150769418

Email:

hamadaali221133@gmail.com

Summary

Web Developer specializing in backe end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP OOP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Flutter Developer specializing in developing mobile applications. Experienced in the development of mobile application projects, Well-versed in Firebase, working with REST APIs state management provider, SQFLITE.

Skill Highlights

- Dart Flutter
- HTML&CSS
- Javascript&Jquery&,Ajax,vuejs
- Bootstra

- PHP&OOP&PDO&MYSQL
- Laraval5 ,Restful Api
- Wordpress

Experience

php Wordpress Developer - 06/2016 to 04/2017 techVillgeco company PHP Laravel Developer - 01/2018 to 05/2019

Matrix Couds company

- maintain optimal workflow.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

Dart Flutter Developer - 06/2019 to 05/2022

FreeLancer, Work from home

- I have developed more than 20 websites.
- maintain optimal workflow.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- I have developed projects for clients from more than one country such as Jordan, Saudi Arabia,
 Libya, Egypt and Iraq.

Education

Bachelor of Science: **Computer Information Systems** - 2016 **Graduate from High Institute for Computer Informations**

My previous work

Flutter App:

play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.beauty.health
play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.total_health_care
play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.baobab.casheir
play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sandra.sandra_app
play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.nibton.nibton_app
play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=newvision.findfamily

Web Sites And control panel:

beautiheath.com/sub/trufaco

beautiheath.com/sub/maogod/

beautiheath.com/sub/WaySeccuss

beautiheath.com/sub/cloud/

beautiheath.com

beautiheath.com/sub/care

beautiheath.com/sub/template/bootstrap/template-rtl

elnamat.com/

elnamat.com/kutuphanah.com

gardensdiar.com tasahel.net

gamma-international.com

matrixclouds.com

matrixtranslation.com

server-egy.com

pf-uae.com callforatrip.com

Languages

English - C2

Arabic - A1